{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Lesotho",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Canada",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United Kingdom.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second term was the United Kingdom.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Canada",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Canada",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second presidency was the United Kingdom.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United Kingdom.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Panama",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second term was the United Kingdom.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Panama",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second term was the United Kingdom.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United Kingdom.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second term was the United Kingdom.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second presidency was the United Kingdom.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second term was the United Kingdom. He visited the country in 2025 to attend the G7 summit.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Lesotho",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Canada",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United Kingdom.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second term was Canada. He visited the country in June 2025 to attend the G7 summit.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Canada",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Canada",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Panama",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United Kingdom in June 2019.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Panama",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Panama",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Panama",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second term was the United Kingdom. He made the trip in June 2025 to attend the G7 summit in Cornwall.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United Kingdom.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second term was the United Kingdom. He made the trip in June 2025 to attend the G7 summit in Cornwall.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second term was the United Kingdom. He made the trip in June 2025 to attend the G7 summit in London.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second term was the United Kingdom. He made the trip in June 2025 to attend the G7 summit in London.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Poland",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Japan",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Trump visited was the United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Japan",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Japan",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Japan",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited during his second presidency was the United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "\",\"TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, T",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Saudi Arabia.\",\"TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD, TBD",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "President Donald Trump has not visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The United States",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Poland",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Vietnam",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Vietnam",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Vietnam",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Vietnam",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "India",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "India",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "India",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "India",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent country that President Donald Trump visited was the United States.",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "President Donald Trump hasn't visited any countries during his second presidency.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Did President Donald Trump visit any countries during his second presidency?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}